I have a relative, he lives in
у меня родственник е сит Он живёт в
Istanbul, he is Turkish Well, as a cousin,
Стамбуле он турецкий Ну как двоюродный
he is my Yes, we Yes, we talked and he says
он мой Да мы Да общались и он говорит
that Erdogan wants to become the ruler of the
что эрдоган он хочет стать правителем
world, he says the Ottoman Empire
мира хочет он говорит Османская империя
was from there and to there and he wants to
была от тада и дотуда и он хочет вот так
do it all like this on the map Hello, man, Hello, What do you
сделать Привет мужик Здравствуйте А чем
talk about,
общаешься да
just like that, in different ways,
просто так по-разному
but a good topic, yes, a good topic, how do you
а хорошая тема да хорошая тема как
count How many Russians have already died in
считайте Сколько уже россиян погибло в
this
этой
war, how many died
войне сколько погибло
Yes, one, two,
Да так
four
раздва четыре
people, you see, you are even Afraid to
человека видите вы даже Боитесь
think about this
подумать над этим
question, I
вопросом кое
understood something, and those four of your
понял а тех которые четыре ваших
friends who died, how did they
знакомых погибли как они
die Well, one, I don’t
погибли Ну так один дроном другой не
know, the other wasn’t
знаю не интересовался остальные не
interested in the rest, to be honest, So especially, and the fact
интересовался если честно Так особо а то
that the drone flew to where they were The drone flew in The drone flew in One
что дроном куда им Дрон
UAZ I also
прилетел Дрон прилетел УАЗик одного тоже
know that it was like that UAZ in a loaf
знаю что так было УАЗик в буханку
Yes, a loaf, yes, I
Да буханку да
understood You are Armenian
понял Ты армянин
Yura, I am an Izid, I am from Armenia It’s
Юра я изид я из Армения
cool, you have a community of Yazidis there
Прикольно у вас там сообщество езидов
now in
есть сейчас в
Russia, in Russia there is, yes, do you belong to
России в России есть да относишься к
them No, I don’t belong to them, but With respect
ним Нет не отношусь но С уважением
I relate to these I understood You
отношусь к этим понял У вас же верования
also have Austrian beliefs yes
ещё за австрийские да
as a belief you have for
как верование у вас за
Striznevo
стризнево
already practically relatives
уже практически родственники
Well where is your father from Armenia No not
Ну отец у вас откуда ва с Армения Нет не
from the territory of the USSR he was, it
с территории СССР он был
turns out, well he died when I was 2
получается ну он умер когда мне было 2
years old, so I didn’t really communicate with him but
года то я с ним как бы не общался но
Mom told me that he was either from
Мама рассказывала что он был или из
Iran or from Turkey somewhere there Isis well
Ирана или из Турции где-то вот там изиды
yes he was not from the territory there there were
ну да он го не с территории там были
some persecutions and that’s why he moved to the
какие-то гонения и он поэтому переехал в
USSR and then Yes
СССР и дальше Да
everything is correct Okay Well done You see
всё правильно Ладно Молодец Вот видишь
how we met yes And how do
как мы встретились да А как сейчас там
you feel about the fact that the War is going on
ты относишься к тому что Война
Well I know I’m in
идёт Ну я знаешь я в
Mariupol What did Mariupol do in the year I
Мариуполе Что делал мариу пром году я по
went there for work I make sofas and
работе туда ездил я делаю диван и
furniture I thought about going there
мебель думал вот поехать там
for s of
за
course it’s a shame that that’s why you
конечно обидно что вот вот а почему ты
Can I be informal yes yes my
Можно на ты да
name is
да меня зовут
Yura And what’s your name
Юра А Вас как зовут
ahen how ahen ahen ahen ahen ahen
ахен как ахен
ahen Yes well
ахен ахен ахен ахен Да ну
such a name is re ma Mom said that my
такой имя такое ре ма мама говорила что
father wanted to name me that
отец хотел так меня назвать
ahn ahn Yes father e  then Ah I'm listening for the first time it's
ахн ахн Да отец е то Ах я первый раз
interesting it's from the Armenian Yazidis
слушаю интересно это из армянских езидов
It's obvious from the Turkish or these Iraqi
Он видно из турецких или этих иракских
there was such a name
там имя такое было
Dale ses now with you one on Yes we
Дале сес сечас с тобой один на Да
speak for Russian
говорим за русский
Ukraine always think as if uh
украи всегда считаю как будто бы ээ
here you know how uh how like seed yes that
здесь знаешь как ээ как как семя да то
is Russia is This is the father Well take as a
есть Россия - это Это отец Ну взять так
family yes But the rest Here is
как семья да А вот остальные Вот это
Ukraine Belarus these are all his children No there on the
Украина Белорусия это всё его дети Нет
contrary there on the contrary look uh Everything
там наоборот там наоборот смотри ээ Всё
came from Kyiv that is the father
пошло из Киева то есть отец - это Киев
was Kyiv and from Kyiv they built other cities
был и из Киева строили другие города вот
all these in Russia which princes were in in
эти все в России которые князья были в в
Kyiv the center Kiev was the father just Kyiv
Киеве центр Киев был отец как раз Киев
was and Belarus Belarus and no Belarus and
был а Беларусь Беларусь и нет Беларусь и
Russia are the children of this father and one of
Россия - это дети этого отца и один из
these child
этих ребёнок
Became this Russia this is the child of Kyiv
Стал вот этот Россия это ребёнок Киева
who
который
became engaged yes and here he came he
стал занимается да вот и он пришёл он
came to the father Yes the father is already a little
пришёл к отцу Да отец немножко уже
adult And this adj yes to
взрослый А этот прил да
take money from the father yes to take his
деньги забирать у отца да забирать его
car the Armed Forces says to take it is simply
машину ВС забирать говорит это просто
this is blasphemy it is impossible so it is against
это богохульство нельзя так это против
really
реально
against Well we are not talking about the
против Ну мы сейчас не говорим за
past now we are talking now Yes the situation is  there is, it
прошлое мы сейчас говорим Да ситуация то
turned out
есть вот получился
like a big country Russia, it is
как страна большая Россия он же
considered, it is recognized by the world, how is this,
считается он же миром признана как это
yes, not by us,
да не нами
mimimi, do not come, just look, the world
мимими не прит как раз смотри мир
thinks that I, I am an international lawyer by education, I
считает что я вот я по образованию юрист
was even an
международник Я в ООН был даже
assistant to the ambassador from Ukraine at the UN and there are
помощником посла от Украины и там есть
documents there I looked, they do not recognize Russia,
документы Я смотрел Россию не признают
how, uh, a great country, they say that Russia is a
как ээ Великую страну говорят что Россия
mixture of Slavic, Turkic and
- это смесь славянских тюркских и
Mongolian peoples, that it should be divided
монгольских народов что она должна быть
into different small countries,
на разные страны маленькие разделена
separately Mongolian peoples, separately
отдельно монгольские народы отдельно
Muslims, Turks, separately Slavs, that's
мусульмане тюрки отдельно славяне вот
how it will be,
так будет
yes Well, you see, now there is a conflict,
да Ну вот понимаешь сейчас конфликт
so people can say everything, yes, but before that it
поэтому люди Всё могут сказать да но до
was a power, now it is also considered a
этого было держава сейчас считается тоже
power No, well, we are not Sorry, please,
держава Нет ну мы не Извини пожалуйста
we interrupt each other and do not understand,
мы перебиваем друг друга и не понимаем
you do not let me finish speaking, I
ты мне не даёшь до конца говориться я
Temperament, this is my Yezidi temperament,
Темперамент это мой езидский темперамент
that's how I am, my mother is generally very
такой я у меня мама вообще очень
calm, she would say, my father was very
спокойна бы она говорила отец был очень
impulsive, I did not see my father, I was 2
импульсивный я не видел отца мне было 2
years old when my father died Yes, and this is generally
года когда отец погиб Да он и это вообще
yes, he died in Afghanistan Well, and you
да он в Афганистане погиб Да ну а ты
know, in Kyiv, we have
знаешь у нас в Киеве есть
Yezidi  seriously In Kyiv there are I know There were
ези серьёзно В Киеве есть я знаю Есть
ISIS and in this in Krasnodar I know
было изиды и в этом в Краснодаре знаю
ISIS there are like too Yes there are a lot of
изиды есть типа тоже Да там очень много
them Yes well in Kyiv there are also
их Да вот ну в Киеве тоже есть
ISIS I even I Even there was uh there was
язи Я даже я Даже был э был праздник
some kind of holiday I came to theirs
какой-то я приходил на ихнюю
this came theirs was like a
эту приезжал ихняя была как оно
cultural center community Yes the holiday is a
культурный центр община Да праз праздник
very interesting holiday Yes in Kyiv there was a woman
очень интересный Да в Киеве там женщина
coming out she was bringing out such flowers a
выходила она выносила такие цветы очень
lot I don't know what it is spring spring was
много я не знаю что это весна весна была
like a holiday Day of the Sun Day of the Sun what is it
как бы праздник День солнца День солнца
called I didn't remember but it's very
как он называется Я не запомнил но очень
beautiful and she brings out flowers just like that A
красиво и она выносит цветы вот так
basket of flowers very flowers and
просто Корзина цветов очень цветы и
passes and gives everyone a flower
проходит и каждому раздаёт цветок
gives everyone a flower as a piece of God
каждому раздаёт цветок как частичку Бога
says I liked it so much wow
говорит мне это так понравилось
well okay that's where are
вау ну хорошо
you from Well where are you from Yes from Odessa from Odessa
вот а Ты откудова сам родом Ну где из Да
Odessa yes Well that's
из Одессы из Одессы Одессы да А ну
it And now Why is the Polish flag on the back
всё А сейчас Почему сзади Польша флаг
this is today The thing is that the
стоит это сегодня Дело в том что
president of Poland said that they will send
президент Польши сказал что отправят в
soldiers to Ukraine and I liked it so much I am the
Украину солдат и мне так понравилось Я
flag of Poland Well you do you want
флаг Польши Ну ты ты хочешь
Poland to send soldiers Yes Poland
чтобы Польша отправил солдат Да Польша
Germany Britain The more the better the
Германия Британия Чем больше тем лучше
more Russians will die faster Yes and
тем больше Русских умрёт быстрее Да а
why do you think Russians  because
почему ты русских считаешь потому что
they attacked my country
они напали на мою страну
they Well look how Well you are a
они Ну вот вот смотри как Да ну вы же
brotherly people No well this is not now and
Братский народ Нет ну это сейчас нет а
before that there are no
до этого нет
Russians I will come Russians were invented by Lenin before
русских приду русских придумал Ленин до
Lenin there were no Russians Russians were invented by
Ленина не было русских русских придумал
Lenin Well now we are two Yazidis Yes we are
Ленин Ну вот сейчас мы два езиды Да мы
talking about Russian Let's talk about Yazidis
говорим о русско Давай о ези говорим
Let's I don't know Yazidis well I now live
Давай я плохо знаю езидов я сейчас живу
in a country that was attacked by Russia in Russian
в стране на которую напала Росси русском
we will talk about Isis Let's talk about Isis Look
языке будем говорить о Изида Давай о
here is our edim - this is Good
Изида Смотри вот наш едим - это Благая
Faith translated as Good Faith Well so I will
вера в переводе Благая Вера Ну так и я
say so that we Yazidis do not have our
скажу так что мы изиды не имеем сейчас
own state now Yes but our How to
своего государства Да но наша Как так
say so I will not say Mafia how is it
сказать не буду говорить Мафия как это
correct to say our cultural
правильно сказать наши культурные
societies yes there are in many cities of
общества да есть во многих городах
Russia Ukraine we keep in Russia there
России Украины мы держим в России очень
are a lot of respected Yazidis who
много есть изидо уважаемых которые
keep both markets and keep business and keep
держат и рынки и держат бизнес и держат
Russians so we will not let ourselves be
русских так что мы не дадим себя
offended Well I myself live in Russia
обидеть Ну я я сам в россие живу я
now
сейчас
I am in Krasnodar there are many Yazidis yes
Я же го в Краснодаре там много езидов да
yes I myself am from Tatarstan with Nave Chelny well
да Я сам из Татарстана с наве Челнов ну
here  I want to move here I liked the climate
сюда хочу переехать здесь мне климат
Well, I'll tell you bro I
Ну за русским скажу братан я плохо не
have no right to be bad with Russians I'm not afraid but
имею права за ним я не то что боись а
we just live with them Yes, they
просто мы живём с ними Да они ко мне
treat me very well I treat them very
очень хорошо относятся Я к ним очень
well there's no such thing why don't you
хорошо нету такого почему вот вас вы не
think that this is a war that happened
думаете что это в война то что Произошло
all this you were simply provoked and
это всё вас просто спровоцировали да и
to each other I say Look, this will
на друг друга я говорю Смотри это это
all
всё
end Yes, do you know who this is who
да закончится Да знаешь кто это кого
look they say America China No, do you know
смотри говорят Америка Китай Нет знаешь
who organized all this Erdogan Who is
кто это всё организовал эрдоган Кто
Erdogan he is a very cunning cockroach with a mustache
эрдоган он очень хитрый таракан усатый
he Look, he did it specifically so that
он Смотри он сделал специально чтобы
Russia would attack Ukraine in order to drive
Россия напала на Украину чтобы выбить
Russia out of
Россию из
Syria earlier Erdogan that he wanted to drive
Сирии раньше эрдоган что он хотел выбить
Russia out of Syria earlier it didn't work out
России и Сирии раньше не получалось У
He and he is cunning cunning this Sultan
него а он хитрый хитрый этот Султан он
what did he do he took Russia says attack
что сделал он взял России говорит напади
Ukraine yes get into Crimea So that's all I will
на Украину да На Крым залезь Так всё я
help you and then Gop and didn't help and
тебе помогу а потом Гоп и не помог и
then Mariupol then all this yes all the
потом Мариуполь потом это всё да все
troops were taken from Syria Wagner and Wagner
войска из Сирии забрали Вагнер и Вагнер
died near Bakhmut then they blew it up
умер под бахмутом потом взорвали
Prigozhina And now Syria everything in 3 days and
пригожина А теперь Сирия всё за 3 дня а
not 11 days and that's it Damascus fell and this Assad
не 11 дней и всё Дамаск пал и этот Асад
fled and now Erdogan says Take the
бежал и теперь эрдоган говорит Забирай
Russian fleet from Tartus and Erdogan
русский флот из Тартус и это эрдоган
did it all cunningly he is a very cunning bug he is
хитро всё сделал он очень хитрый жук он
more than that look Erdogan has
больше того смотри у эрдогана в Чёрном
ships left in the Black Sea And the Russians have none
море остались корабли А у русских не
left They were all
остались Все
destroyed Erdogan is everything
уничтожены эрдоган он вс он хитрый жук
he is a cunning bug he deceived everyone and the USA and China and the Yazidis and the
он всех и США обманул и Китай обманул и
Kurds and the
езидов обманул и курдов обманул и
Russians deceived everyone Erdogan is a
русских обманул всех обманул эрдоган -
very cunning bug that's why he specially
это очень хитрый жук вот он специально
lured the Russians so that they would make this
заманил русских чтобы они сделали эту
war and now he has driven the Russians out of Syria Yes he
войну и теперь выбил русских из Сирий Да
forbade them to pass through the Basfor
запретил им проходить через басфор
Dardanelles and their ships Why can't Russia go
дарданелы и ихним суда Почему Россия не
to the Black Sea if it brought
может в Чёрное море если бы она привела
all its ships it would have captured Odessa
все свои корабли она бы одесу захватила
and Erdogan says No I won't let you through the Basfor
а эрдоган говорит Нет я вас через бафо
Dardanelles
дарне не
That's a cunning Sultan very cunning
пропущу Это хитрый Султан очень хитрый
he says Istanbul is the Center of the World that's
он говорит Стамбул - это Центр мира вот
really what he says I am  I
реально он такое говорит я я
looked at my relatives sit He lives
смотрел у меня родственники сит Он живёт
in Istanbul he is Turkish Well as a cousin
в Стамбуле он турецкий Ну как двоюродный
he is Mo yes we talked and he says that
он Мо да мы да общались и он говорит что
Erdogan he wants to become the ruler of the world
эрдоган он хочет стать правителем мира
wants he says the Ottoman Empire was
хочет он говорит Османская империя была
from there and up to there and he wants to do it all like that on the map
отда и дотуда и он хочет так по карте
and Erdogan is a
сделать и эрдоган
horse
конской
empire Well the Ottoman Empire to be honest is
империи Ну Османская империя если честно
also from there well Our history since
родом тоже ну Наша история вот поскольку
I know our history begins with Turkey
я знаю наша история начинается с Турции
my great-grandfather is from there yes yes Oh
мой прадед
they They ran towards
отту да да О они Они прибежали в сторону
Armenia But my great-grandfather uh he is from
Армения Но мой прадед ээ он из из
Derbak this is where is this Turkey
дербак это где это Турция
And from there they convinced towards
А вот они оттуда убеждали в сторону
Armenia Well during This is also the
Армения Ну во время Вот это это тоже
genocide of Armenians yes yes and there everyone and Armenians
геноцид армян дада да и там все и армяне
Turks these Kurds Yids everyone everyone everyone Yes And so he you
турки эти курды иды все все все Да И вот
know how his history
он он знаешь как у него история очень
was very tough Yes he his friend comes to
жёсткий был Да он его друг приходит к
him He says Listen your dad mom was
нему Он говорит Слушай твой папу маму
killed there this Come on we need to run away from here
убили там это Давай надо отсюда убежать
Ottoman Empire st and he takes his
Османская империя ул и он берёт своего
brother and son yes and they were both the same age
брата и сына да и они оба одно возрасте
and he two  beats and runs away runs away
были и он двоих бьёт и убегает убегает
he understands that he can't handle two Dani is lying now
он понимает что он двоих не потянет Дани
they will all fall down
сечас вром упадут их всех утв
in Turkey Yes he leaves Sina and his brother
в Турции Да он оставляет Сина и брат
says My parents killed him says I have no
говорит У меня родители убили говорит
parents I have a brother I will marry him I will have
родителе нету у меня брато Я пожени у
children Yes he leaves his son And his
меня будет детей Да сына он оставляет А
son's name was
сына звали
Herman And so he leaves his son and
Герман И вот он сына оставляет и брата
takes his brother together they go to the side Armenia
берёт вдвоём они в сторону Армения
gets to Armenia that's our history that's
попадает в Армению вот наша история вот
where we already know from yes that's further already to
мы оттуда уже знаем да вот дальше уже до
our that's our great-grandfather was we do
нашего вот это прадеда был мы уже дальше
n't know further Well that's how our roots are from there
не знаем Ну так-то вот наши корни оттуда
Yes we got into that in Armenia
Да мы попадали попадали в эту в Армения
and in the year when the earthquake
и в во ВОМ году когда землетрясение
happened and Spitak Yes Spitak was yes yes that's where
случилось а Спитак Да Спитак был да
we are from Lenin Yes And that's when
да вот мы с ленана Да И вот когда
the earthquake was we are in Uzbekistan
землетрясение был мы по Узбекистане жи
we live in Tashkent We went there to
ташкен Мы туда поехали ташкен
live in Tashkent in short 15 years well according to our
жить короче 15 лет вот ну по нашей
history even yes about grandfather yes every 15
истории даже да про деда да каждые 15
years we radically change our life that's
лет мы кардинально Меняем наш жизнь это
Look yes there is such a thing in the
Смотри да это есть такое
Yezidi it's called that I read in
езидском оно называется что я читал в
translation that it's like  Jews have something
переводе что это как у евреев есть что
they have
они с
their own State from China and we have to
киталия свою Государство и мы должны мы
we have to this And where is the
должны это А где г кто даст нам вот
state who will give it to us you see the state And who to the Jews who to the Jews Yes
видишь госу А кто евреям кто евреям Да
they didn't ask for it they came and
они не спрашивали чтоб дали они пришли и
said we take our own we have something written in our book
сказали мы берём своё у нас в книга
Well that's what I think That's why I
такое Ну вот я считаю Вот почему я
think if we ourselves are a peaceful nation we have no
считаю если сами Мирная нация у нас нету
enemies We we don't think about solutions Yes not the Duma to
врагов Мы мы не думаем раство Да не Дума
buy a machine gun soldiers tanks to fight to
купить автомат солдат танки воевать
take away someone we don't have it in our heads That's it The
кого-то отнять у нас нету в голове Вот
Yazidis Yeah That's because we are
это да У езидов Угу Вот потому что мы
very peaceful people yes to us it doesn't mean anything at all
очень мирные люди да нам нам это вообще
Yes That's all yes yes we have no enemies here the
сего да да вот у нас нету врагов вот у
Yazidi has no enemy well if if we
езида нету врага вот ну если если так
take it honestly I know why
взять честно я знаешь к чему это
we have no land no enemy
у нас нет земли нет
Yes no no enemy ours we got the world the
врага Да нет нет врага наше нам мир
world Why do we Yes a piece of land to take away from someone we
мир Зачем нам Да кусок земли у кого-то
need to fight all this we need to kill
отнять воевать надо это всё уби надо
through the state registration plate the world We
через грз мир Нам
got it I want to
достался Я
go to Australia I want to come to Ukraine
за захочу поеду в австрали пожи захочу
Why did Russia attack Ukraine
Зачем Россия напала на Украину
then this is a very difficult question
тогда вот это это очень тяжёлый вопрос
few can answer it especially since
на него мало кто может ответить тем боле
we are the wisest people we can
мы эи самый мудрый народ мы можем
answer
ответить на
everything Well I was looking for an answer in Mariupol Yes I did
всё Ну я вот ответ искал Мариуполе Да я
n't find an
не нашёл там
answer there I wanted to find an answer there By the way I was
ответа Я хотел там найти ответа Я кстати
in Mariupol I
в Мариуполе
saw you know what I also have
был видел знаешь что у меня тоже есть
friends from Mariupol they say they
знакомые из Мариуполя они говорят
show on TV that Mariupol was
показывают по телевизору что Мариуполя
rebuilt nothing like that they made three houses
отстроили ничего подобного три дома
and show them from all angles
сделали и показывают их со всех ракурсов
on TV and that's it No not me I with my own eyes I with my
по телевизору и всё не Да не я Я своими
own eyes there I
глазами я Своими глазами там я 3 месяца
lived there for 3 months Marple is being built very well
там жил Марпл очень хорошо строится
very well and fully And there is high-quality
очень хорошо и полно И там качественно
construction there not like there And how many people were
строится не то что там А сколько людей
killed there in Mariupol lived 500,000
убили там в Мариуполе жило 500.000
half a million people remained 100,000 killed
полмиллиона людей осталось 100.000 убили
400,000 killed killed destroyed
400.000 убили убили уничтожили
not they left them so they left So how did they
не они уехали их так уехали Так а как их
why did they leave if they were liberated I don't
зачем они уехали если их освободили Я не
understand well they left can they come back
понимаю ну уехали могут вернуться
please Well how do they come back Yes
пожалуйста Ну как они возвращаются Да
look there was half a million left  100,000
смотри был полмиллиона осталось 100.000
somehow they were liberated in such a way that they left I
как-то их так освободили что они уехали
can't understand why so well
не могу понять почему
people there you know how it was they did
так ну ну люди там знаешь как было они
n't expect that it would be so long yes It
не ожидали что так долго будет да Это и
will be full scale such a war Yes they
будет полно масштабно такое война Да они
think so 2-t and quickly in And that's it yes and it
думаю так 2-т и быстро во И всё да а оно
remains like that and somehow bad
так вот остаётся и как-то плохо
yes well they had to leave Well please I
да ну пришлось им уйти Ну пожалуйста
can return And if
могу верну А если тебя вот в Краснодар
NATO troops come to liberate you in Krasnodar and
придут освобождать войска НАТО и будут
bomb your Krasnodar where will you go
бомбить твой Краснодар ты куда поедешь
Well peace I got I will come to you
Ну мир Мне достался я приеду к вам
bro in Odessa why the hell do we need you in
братан в Одессу наху ты нам нужен в
Odessa I'm
Одессе честно
telling you honestly and what if you are against it Well you are a
говорю а ну ты против будешь Ну ты
citizen of Russia why are you in Odessa I'm not
гражданин России ско вы в Одессе не
telling you honestly whether you are an Isid or a Jew I don't
честно говорю хоть изид хоть еврей не
know if you are from Russia Why do we need
знаю если ты из России Зачем нам в
Odessa you don't come here don't think about
Одессу ты на не едь сюда не думай
somewhere Go to Armenia go to Odessa don't
куда-то Иди в Армению едь в Одессу не
go Well why is it like that yes you
едь Ну а почему вот так да ты вопрос
put the question to us not ed I am I am because
поставил к нам не ед Я я я се пото что
you are you are killing now you are
вы вы сейчас убиваете вы на мою Одесса
dropping a big bomb on my Odessa  I flew to kindergarten
бомбу скидывает большую бомба на садик
and you say I'll come here and they'll tear
прилетела а ты говоришь я приеду сюда
you apart I'll be the first to leave
так тебя тут порвут Я тебя первый выйду
You came to Odessa What do you
Ты что в Одессу приехал Ты что
mean if you come and say I'm from
вообще я если ты приедешь и скажешь я из
Russia Good afternoon I'll take you to the station
России Добрый день я тебя на вокза
Why did I do anything bad What did I
возьму А зачем а я те плохого ничего не
do anything good Did I do anything
сде А че а хорошего ничего не сделал Я
good What did you do good good
ли хорошего А что ты сделал
Yes you're a bomb you're
хорошего хорошего Да ты бом ты бомбу
dropping a bomb on my city
скидываешь на мой город
if Odessa is occupied You'll also be going to
ездишь если Одессу оккупирует Ты тоже
bring sofas Yes you'll bring one you'll
будешь ездить диваны возить Да иты
say They'll bomb
Привезёшь скажешь Они они будут бомбить
Odessa and then you'll come I
Одессу а потом ты приедешь Я вам диван
brought you a sofa Yes go away with your sofa
привёз Да пошёл ты на со своим диваном
your
свой
Krasnodar
Краснодар
shist on my Telegram right now axis win
шисть на мий Telegram прямо зараз ось
and
вин а
popok this is very and very important YouTube
попок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube
Zaga us through SRG OR in your ban and very
Зага нас через срг ор в твый бан и дуже
many videos I don't show people at times I don't
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams that's why
показуе информация про стримы тому для
we Mali operational link
того щоб ми Мали оперативний звязок
is written right now and while there in telegram
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
okm video tezh va and useful information
окм видео ще теж ва и корисна информация
and we pon va trima
и мы пон ва трима
sing operational link independently in that
пой оперативный звязок незалежно в того
chi will show you the process YouTube Glory to
чи покаже вам проце YouTube Слава
Ukraine subscribe
Украине подпишись